<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Flock137</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Flock137</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.154.5</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Failed attempt on performing Hardware Forensics (STM32)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/stm32_failed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/stm32_failed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I chose to start my hardware hacking journey with an attempt to live debugging a piece of hardware. As I am waiting for the necessary parts I need to arrive, I did some emulations of the STM32, so I might have the binary ready to flash the binary into the hardware by the times the parts arrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As weird as it is to write about a failed attempt on a blog post, this is written to at least temporary record what I did, for potential future references. The code for this attempt would not be released, as I definitely do not want to embarrase myself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ai_gon3_r0ug3 Writeup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ai_gon3_r0ug3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ai_gon3_r0ug3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a Private CTF organized under the collaboration between HackerOne and HackTheBox that focus only on the AI category.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;re-car-ai&#34;&gt;Re-car AI&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have been tasked with pentesting the largest used car listing website in your area. They have recently implemented an AI chatbot in their listing page to help users with common questions. The website&amp;rsquo;s policy is not to disclose the seller&amp;rsquo;s information unless the user is logged in. Can you find a way to bypass the filters and reveal the seller&amp;rsquo;s phone number by asking the chatbot? Flag format: &lt;code&gt;HTB{xxx-xxxx-xxx}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girls-in-CTF Writeup - Forensics &amp; AI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/gctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/gctf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To encourage and celebrate women/girls in cyber security, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.rehack.xyz/&#34;&gt;Re:Hack&lt;/a&gt; has organized this girls-only-CTF. As a woman, I really appreciate this effort and it feels incredibly inspiring. This is the first time that myself see so many girls and women gather in one place and all are incredibly passionate about this very technical field. So, I would like to give a very special thank-you to the organizers and all the challenge writers involved to make this sort of event possible.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScriptCTF Writeup - Forensics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/scriptctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/scriptctf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;pdf-author-connor-chang&#34;&gt;pdf (Author: Connor Chang)&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Description: so sad cause no flag in pdf&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The challenge attachment can be found here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/scriptCTF/scriptCTF2025-OfficialWriteups/blob/main/Forensics/pdf/attachments/challenge.pdf&#34;&gt;https://github.com/scriptCTF/scriptCTF2025-OfficialWriteups/blob/main/Forensics/pdf/attachments/challenge.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this challenge, you can open up Firefox to view the hint in the given PDF, but for this approach, we won&amp;rsquo;t need to use it. All we have to do is using &lt;code&gt;binwalk&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;binwalk -e challenge.pdf 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the extracted folder, click on (or &lt;code&gt;cat&lt;/code&gt;) the text file (&lt;code&gt;11B&lt;/code&gt; or something similar), the flag is in there
&lt;img alt=&#34;alt text&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/posts/scriptctf/images/challenge.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How did I repair an (Arch) Linux bootloader twice</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/bootloader_failed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/bootloader_failed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction-updating-bios-got-linux-overwritten&#34;&gt;Introduction: Updating BIOS, got Linux overwritten&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After I updated my BIOS, it happened to auto turn on secure boot, bitlocker again and overwrite the bootloader on my Linux partition on a separated disk.
Not to mention, I no longer see my &lt;code&gt;systemd&lt;/code&gt; bootloader screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;disable-bitlocker-key&#34;&gt;Disable bitlocker key&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To disable bitlocker key (not decrypt the whole drive), so the windows partition won&amp;rsquo;t ask you bitlocker password over and over again when you dual-boot:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recover corrupted USB in Linux terminal (required complete data wipe)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/usb_uncorrupted/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/usb_uncorrupted/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;step-1&#34;&gt;Step 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;lsblk
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;The USB would likely to be something like &lt;code&gt;sda&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;sdb&lt;/code&gt; (the same name with number is a partition). The easiest way to figure out which is your thumb drive is the size.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;step-2&#34;&gt;Step 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the system mount any of your partition, you need to unmount them first before wiping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;# Replace sdX1 with your actual partition identifier (e.g., sdb1)
sudo umount /dev/sdX1
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;h1 id=&#34;step-3&#34;&gt;Step 3&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use &lt;code&gt;wipefs&lt;/code&gt; command to completely erase all partition tables and filesystem signatures from the drive.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revive FlareVM Network Connection (VirtualBox)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flarevm_network/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flarevm_network/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Normally, installing a FlareVM won&amp;rsquo;t mutate your network connection. However, for some reason, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to access network inside the VM. This could have caused by one or a couple of reasons:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Non-fatal errors occured during installation (I was supposed to look at the screen during all process, but it took 6h to finish&amp;hellip;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The recovery function of Windows got forced shut down to fulfill installation prerequisites, so it can not intervene and autofix the network issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A driver &amp;ldquo;Other&amp;rdquo; was spotted to be missing after FlareVM completely finish its installation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;virtualbox-network-setting-walkthrough&#34;&gt;VirtualBox network setting walkthrough&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may like to switch to either NAT or Bridged Adapter. In the Adapter type, choose something along the line of &amp;ldquo;Intel&amp;hellip; Desktop&amp;rdquo;, or if you don&amp;rsquo;t know what to choose, just leave the default option.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merging multiple singular .ics files into one in Linux</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/calendar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Step 1: Gather your individual .ics files in a folder. Open the terminal in the said folder. Type this in your console.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;# Comhbine all .ics to a new text file
cat *.ics &amp;gt; temp.txt 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Step 2: If you check with &lt;code&gt;cat temp.txt&lt;/code&gt; you can see there is this weird string that you need to get rid off: &lt;code&gt;END:VCALENDARBEGIN:VCALENDAR&lt;/code&gt;. Use &lt;code&gt;cat temp.txt | grep -v DARBEG &amp;gt; temp1.txt&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Step 3: For my case, I also need to:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
